BOOM
FLIP
JOJO'S BIZARRE ADVENTURE
DIAMOND IS UNBREAKABLE
A demon's crept into
our everyday life
It's about to take away
something precious
Our peace has already
crumbled long ago
So casually, so nonchalantly
It's taken from us
before we know it
If we want it back,
now's the chance
With the sharpness of
the piercing arrow
The beauty of two souls united
Wherever you go, chase you
Whenever, chase you
I will chase you
Nowhere to escape
Start running, I will chase you
Tomorrow, chase you
My fists will be the one
to show you
Tenacity decides
who will win or lose
So I chase you
EPISODE 15
LET'S GO TO
THE MANGA ARTIST'S HOUSE, PART 2
I CANNOT ATTACK
THE MANGA ARTIST, ROHAN KISHIBE
CANNOT
HEAVEN'S DOOR
IF JOSUKE HIGASHIKATA CAUSES
TROUBLE FOR ROHAN KISHIBE,
I WILL BURN MYSELF TO DEATH
SECONDS
YOUR KID IS SICK, RIGHT?
I'll PUSH YOUR CAR.
NOW STEP ON THE GAS.
ONCE YOU GAIN TRACTION,
DON'T STOP. JUST GUN IT…
OR YOU'LL GET STUCK AGAIN.
ROHAN KISHIBE'S
PINK DARK BOY
— SUSPENSION NOTICE —
SORRY!
THANK YOU FOR YOUR CONTINUED
READERSHIP OF PINK DARK BOY.
DUE TO PERSONAL MATTERS,
OUR PUBLICATION WILL BE
SUSPENDED FOR ONE MONTH.
(FROM THE EDITORS)
EPISODE 16
LET'S GO HUNTING!